Alright, the next part of this section, I'm actually going to go over the TypeScript edition of this.
好的，本节的下一部分，我就真的要向你展示这个的 TypeScript 版本了
But for all intents and purposes, you've successfully created your first Hardhead project,
但不管怎么讲，你都已经成功创建了你的第一个 Hardhat 项目了
you've done a ton of amazing things. In this lesson,
你已经在这节课中完成了许多了不起的事情了
let's do a quick refresher of what we've learned so far,
现在让我们快速回顾一下目前为止我们学到的内容
we learned how to spin up our own hard hat projects.
我们学习了如何启动我们的 Hardhat 项目
And now we can run yarn, hard hat
现在我们可以运行 "yarn hardhat"
and see a list of the tasks and different things that we can do with hard hat.
并查看可以使用 Hardhat 执行的 task 以及其他操作的列表
We learned that hard hat looks for this hard hat.config.js.
我们知道了 Hardhat 会寻找这个 "hardhat.config.js"
And this is sort of the entry point for any task that we run that starts with hard hat,
这是我们运行任何以 "hardhat" 开头的 task 的入口
we learned we can add our contracts to this contracts folder.
我们学习了可以添加我们的合约到这个 "contracts" 文件夹
And then we compile it by running yarn, art half compile,
然后可以执行 "yarn hardhat compile" 来编译它
we learned that all the compliation goes into the artifacts and then the cache as well.
我们学习了所有的编译结果都会存放在 "artifacts" 和 "cache" 中
And if we want to clean reset, we can either delete these two files
并且如果我们想清空和重置，那么可以删除这两个文件
or just run yarn, hard hat clean.
或是执行 "yarn hardhat clean"
So we learned that we can use scripts or tasks
我们还学习了如何使用脚本和 task
to actually deploy, interact and do things with our smart contracts.
来部署，交互和处理我们的智能合约
We also learned that I'm going to be using scripts for the rest of this course.
我们还学到了在这个课程的剩余部分我都将使用脚本
But if you want, you could absolutely use tasks as well.
但如果你想的话，也完全可以使用 task
I've asked this question a million times what's the difference?
我已经问过了无数次这二者有什么区别
Nobody really seems to know what the main difference is.
但似乎没有人真正知道它们的主要区别是什么
But I think the main difference is that tasks are for plugins.
不过我认为主要区别是 task 用于插件
And scripts are for your local development Mart, that is mind limiter,
而脚本用于你的本地开发模式，这是我的看法
we learned that we can import a whole bunch of things,
我们还学习了可以导入这么一大堆东西到我们的脚本中
including tasks from hard hat in our scripts,
其中就包括 Hardhat 的 task
and we can work with our async functions to grab our contracts and deploy them,
并且我们可以使用异步函数来获取我们的合约并部署它们
we actually then can programmatically verify them using hard hat and using hard hat plugins.
我们还可以使用 Hardhat 和 Hardhat 的插件来程序化地验证它们
And then additionally, we can interact with our contracts very similar to how we did it with ethers.
此外我们还可以使用与 ethers 非常相似的方法与合约进行交互
We wrote a wonderful verification script.
我们编写了一个非常棒的验证脚本
And we also wrote our own task,
还编写了一个我们自己的 task
we wrote our first test for this whole space.
我们为整个空间编写了第一个测试
And we showed what our tests are going to look like moving forward.
并展示了我们未来的测试形式
And we talked a little bit about their importance.
我们还稍微谈了点测试的重要性
And I really should stress that
并且我十分强调
writing good tests is going to be the difference between a really professional environment and kind of a side project.
是否编写了一个好的测试是一个项目专业还是业余的主要区别
Whenever I audit smart contracts,
每当我审计智能合约时
or whenever I'm given a project for someone to tell me to take a look at.
或是每当有人给我一个项目让我去瞧一瞧的时候
The first thing I look at is the readme, of course.
我的第一件事是阅读 README，这是当然的了
And the second thing I look at is the tests.
而第二件事就是查看它的测试
And if tests aren't good, I usually tell them,
如果测试写的不好，我就会告诉他们
hey, you need to go back to the drawing board, and you need to level up your tests.
嘿，你得重头开始，并且提升一下你的测试水平
So tests are really really important, especially for this space,
因此测试非常非常的重要，尤其是对这个领域来说
we learned about a couple of more environment variables we can use.
我们还学习了另外几个可用的环境变量
We learned about a couple of tools to see how good our tests are one of them being coverage.
以及几个用于检查测试质量的工具，其中一个是 "coverage"
We also learn about a gas reporter
我们还学习了有关 "gas-reporter" 的内容
to see how much it's going to cost us when we actually deploy to a real network.
它可以查看我们在实际网络上进行部署时的花费
We learned a ton about the hard hat config,
我们学习了大量有关 "hardhat.config" 的知识
and how there are multiple networks that we can add add to our hard heads,
以及如何在 Hardhat 中添加多个网络
we can make our project our EVM code, work with any network out there,
这样我们就可以使我们项目的 EVM 代码用于任何网络上
we started working with dev dependencies instead of regular dependencies.
我们开始使用 "devDependencies" 而不是常规依赖项
Now, READMEs are something that I'm not really going to go over too deeply in here.
README 并不是一个我现在要深入讲解的东西
But READMEs are sort of like the welcome page of your GitHub repository,
README 有点像是一个 GitHub 仓库的欢迎页面
and really should give you an understanding of what your code does.
要能帮助他人了解你的代码是干什么的
Being a part of the web through space. And being a part of the blockchain ecosystem
要想成为 Web3 和区块链领域的一部分
is really more than just you coding your stuff by yourself.
仅仅是自己会写代码是完全不够的
You want other people to interact and engage with your code and engage with your projects.
你得与其他人进行交互并促使他们参与你的代码和项目
I haven't showed you how to use GitHub yet.
我还没有向你们展示如何使用 GitHub
But don't worry, we're going to
但不用担心，很快就会讲到
but if you look at my heart had simple storage readme.
如果你查看我的 "hardhat-simple-storage" 的 README
If you scroll down,
如果你往下拉
usually, you really want to have a Getting Started section
通常你会希望有一个“开始使用” ("Getting Started") 部分
where you define how to set up all the code and how to set everything up
里面包含了如何配置全部代码以及如何进行设置
a Quickstart section,
还有一个“快速上手” ("Quickstart") 部分
and maybe a usage section and some testing section,
也许还会有一个“使用” ("Useage") 部分和一个“测试” ("Testing") 部分
which teaches people how to actually use and interact with your code.
这些部分能教会人们如何实际使用你的代码并与之交互
Since we're just learning more of the code part
因为我们现在更多地还是在进行代码的学习
and not so much the readme part.
而不是 README 环节
For now, we're not going to go over how to make a fantastic readme.
所以目前我不会深入讲解如何把 README 做的出彩
However, I will leave a link in the GitHub repository associated with this course,
不过，我会在课程关联的 GitHub 仓库里留下一个链接
link to this best readme template.
它会链接到这个最佳的 README 模板下
It really is a fantastic readme template
它真的是一个很不错的 README 模板
that you can copy to any of your projects to make them look really good and give them a really good setup,
你可以把它复制到你的项目中并进行适当的配置，以使你的 README 也变得很好看
so that other developers can come to your project,
这样其它开发者就可以参与到你的项目中
and learn and participate with what you're coding.
并了解和参与你的编程工作
But all right, you have learned an absolute ton,
但话说回来，你已经学了很多东西了
you should be incredibly proud of yourself,
你应该为自己感到无比自豪
and incredibly excited that you've made it this far.
并为自己能走到这一步而感到兴奋
Now I'm going to jump into the TypeScript section here.
现在我要进入到 TypeScript 部分了
So for those of you who are coding along with TypeScript,
对于那些要使用 TypeScript 的人来说
feel free to follow along.
你可以选择跟进
For those of you who are not,
如果你不是的话
you just finished the Basic section on hard hit, but stick around
你刚刚只是完成了 Hardhat 的基础部分，所以请保持势头
the next to heart out sections are going to be the ones that really fine grain and hone your skills,
接下来的两个 Hardhat 章节才是真正精细化以及磨练你技术的部分
and give you all the fundamentals for working with these frameworks.
它们会为你提供使用这个框架所需的所有基本知识
So be sure to follow along with the next two sections,
所以请务必跟上接下来的两个章节
we've got a ton more fantastic content for you,
里面还有更精彩的内容等着你
we are just beginning to get deeper into the smart contract ecosystem.
我们才刚刚开始深入智能合约的生态系统
So take that lap, get that coffee, and I'll see you soon.
所以休息一下，喝杯咖啡，待会儿再见